RONAK JILKA

Mumbai ,Kandivali West +91- 9819073142 | ronakjilka@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-oriented and problem solver with 3 years of experience building and maintaining software and software architecture. Perfection-obsessed Software Developer, My interests range from technology to design, I like to code things from scratch, and enjoy bringing ideas to life in the browser.

	CODE COMPETENCIES
	CORE COMPETENCIES
✓ HTML/ CSS	JavaScript
✓ React	React Native
Python	✓ Node JS
✓ Java	✓ Git
	PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TechExcel Software Solutions Pvt Ltd

Full Stack Developer | November, 2020 - Present

- Worked on Developing a KYC Software for Stocks & Commodity Brokers
- Lead on Project for Stock Market Charts
- Managing code on Github
- Responsible for code review of other teammates. Work on frontend using ReactJS and write test cases using Jest.

HOM Token

Freelance - Frontend Developer | June, 2020 - October 2020

- Design and develop the web applications with React JS and Node Js
- Crafting stateless APIs for the best performance in web and mobile application
- Working with AWS SQS and AWS RDS
- Working with BlockChain

Digital Crown

Frontend Developer February, 2020 - June, 2020

- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features
- Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency
- Design, build, and maintain high performance, reusable, and reliable Java code

Edjoy

Frontend Developer | June, 2019 - January, 2020

- Managed complex projects from start to finish Collaborated with other designers
- Translated requirements into polished, high-level designs
- Bug fixing and improving application performance
- Worked with outside data sources and APIs

EDUCATION

2015 - 2020 | Shivaji University

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science

Master of Science - Computer Science